https://www.upmconveyors.co.uk/privacy-policy/

+44 (0)1753 548801
sales@upm.co.ukThis Privacy Policy sets out how we, UPM Conveyors Ltd, obtain, store and use your personal information.By using our website, https://www.upmconveyors.co.uk/, you agree to the use and treatment of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.How we collect or obtain personal information about youWe collect personal information when you provide it to us:when you fill in a form on our websitewhen you contact us by phone, email or in writingwhen you use post or react to our social media channelswhen you order goods or services from us  Where permitted by law we may also receive information about you from third parties such as affiliates, business partners, credit and fraud checking services as well as third parties with whom we have had no prior contact.How we collect anonymous information about your behaviourWe indirectly collect anonymous information about you to get a general idea of how our website is performing, this information is not linked directly to you but third party services outside of our control may use this to profile your activities and provide relevant advertising in other platforms. This may occur at any time while you are browsing our website.CookiesCookies are small packets of information stored on your device used to keep a record of your history while using a particular website. This could be used to tailor page content to your past behaviour, to keep hold of information that lets us know if you’ve logged in, or to let us know what items you’ve added to a shopping cart. The cookies under our control are only visible to you and to our website.While you are free to disable cookies on your browser, doing so may impact the functionality of this and other websites you visit and as such is not recommended.Third Party CookiesWe use other services to help us to deliver our website, and they may also store cookies on your device to display personalised content or to gather statistics while you are visiting our website. We’ll list those in detail and give a brief overview of why and how we use them below.Contact FormsInformation you submit to us on a contact form will be sent by email to our staff, and will remain stored on the website or within backups for a maximum of 60 days just in case the email doesn’t get to us. If we intend to retain information for marketing purposes we’ll ask you first and give details on the form.User submitted Comments & ReviewsYou can submit comments on our content if you want to. Normal visitors will be able to read anything that you post, and the name under which you have submitted the comment. You may use a pseudonym if you prefer to remain anonymous. We may ask for your email address to verify but we will never make this public.Third-Party Services we may share data withThird Party Analysis ToolsWe use the following third party services to track and monitor visitor flows and behaviour.Google AnalyticsGoogle analytics provides us with detailed web statistics and real time monitoring to help us measure the performance of our web site. Google makes a point to only share non-personally identifiable information with their partners. Google’s privacy policy is available in full at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/Social Media ServicesSome pages of our web site may connect with the following social media services. These may use third party cookies to connect with your own account to provide personalised content.YouTubeWe use functionality from YouTube to display personalised content, or to allow you to share content with your friends. We do not have any direct access to information relating to your YouTube account. For detail on YouTube’s privacy policy please visit https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines&gl=GBEmail Communication ServicesWe use the following third party services to send email, so they will indirectly have access to a portion of your activity and some of your personal details. Once an email leaves systems we use directly, it may be routed through any number of others systems.MailGunMailgun provides a means for our web site to send email to staff and visitors, as such information will be passed through their services. Email content is retained for logging purposes for a short time. Mailgun’s privacy policy can be reviewed in full at https://www.mailgun.com/privacy-policyOur DetailsOur company name is UPM Conveyors Ltd and we operate from 5 Elder Way, Langley Business Park, Slough, SL3 6EP, United Kingdom. You can contact us directly via this web site, via email at steve.wicks@upm.co.uk or via telephone on 01753 548801.Questions or ComplaintsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us through the channels listed above.Latest News UPM – Another successful bespoke project with Lenham Storage UPM Report On A Record Year Automation Gains from the Exhibits | PPMA Total Show UPM Conveyors Exhibiting At PPMA 2019 January Coverage in Machinery Update MagazinePartners’ NewsBritish Plastics NewsPlastikcity NewsNew Technology HallConveyorsFood Approved ConveyorsStainless Steel ConveyorsTurnkey Conveyor SystemsRoller ConveyorsRadius ConveyorsMerging Conveyor SystemsRotary Tables & Lazy Susan ConveyorsHMWPE ConveyorsCooling & Metal Detector ConveyorsWeighing, Counting & Box Filling ConveyorsQuick Belt RemovalVibratory & Bulk Feeders3D CAD Design SoftwareOur Affiliates
© 2020 UPM Conveyors | Terms & Conditions of Sale |
Privacy & Cookies | Website by BritWeb
By using this site you agree to the terms of our privacy policy - More InfoNo problem
